[
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff85",
    "correctAnswer": "Lincoln",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Omaha", "Nebraska City", "Kearney"],
    "question": "What is the capital of Nebraska?",
    "tags": ["us_states", "cities", "usa", "geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "number ":4,
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950129",
    "correctAnswer": "Mecca",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Tehran", "Dubai", "Riyadh"],
    "question": "To where do Muslims make pilgrimage?",
    "tags": ["society_and_culture"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950ac4",
    "correctAnswer": "Latvia",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Kyrgyzstan", "Tajikistan", "Uzbekistan"],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Russia?",
    "tags": ["russia", "geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501ae",
    "correctAnswer": "Animal Farm",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Clockwork Orange",
      "L'Ingénu",
      "Nineteen Eighty-Four"
    ],
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mr. Jones, of the Manor Farm, had locked the hen-houses for the night, but was too drunk to remember to shut the pop-holes.'?",
    "tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcc4",
    "correctAnswer": "Austronesian",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Indo-European", "Niger–Congo", "Kra–Dai"],
    "question": "The language 'Tagalog' belongs to which language family?",
    "tags": ["language", "society_and_culture"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6293ebf07f41d6338b96eecb",
    "correctAnswer": "Roman Emperor who accepted the Christian religion.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Holy Roman Emperor who united Germany.",
      "Ottoman Emperor who conquered Istanbul.",
      "French King who expelled the British from mainland Europe."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following describes Constantine the Great?",
    "tags": ["people", "history", "leaders"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950055",
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Nicklaus",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Tiger Woods", "Phil Mickelson", "Bobby Jones"],
    "question": "Who was first to win the US Masters five times?",
    "tags": ["golf", "people", "sport"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507c7",
    "correctAnswer": "Harrison Ford",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Mark Hamill", "Brad Pitt", "Pedro Pascal"],
    "question": "Which actor originally played the role of Han Solo in Star Wars?",
    "tags": ["star_wars", "film", "acting", "general_knowledge", "film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fba1",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Circle of Life\" by Elton John",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"SpongeBob SquarePants Theme\" by Painty the Pirate",
      "\"Let's Go Crazy\" by Prince and The Revolution",
      "\"What I Got\" by Sublime"
    ],
    "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Nants ingonyama bagithi Baba / Sithi uhm ingonyama...\"?",
    "tags": ["songs", "lyrics", "music"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625741333d2f5c16bfb88345",
    "correctAnswer": "A human soldier is sent from 2029 to 1984 to stop an almost indestructible cyborg killing machine.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Marine observes the effects of war on his fellow recruits from their boot camp training to fighting in a war.",
      "The lives of mob hitmen, a boxer, a gangster and his wife, and a pair of bandits intertwine in four tales.",
      "Historical events unfold from the perspective of an Alabama man with an IQ of 75."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie The Terminator?",
    "tags": ["film", "film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950bd1",
    "correctAnswer": "Lordi",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Nightwish", "Poets of the Fall", "Stratovarius"],
    "question": "Which Finnish hard rock band released the album 'Deadache'?",
    "tags": ["music"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd95",
    "correctAnswer": "Unchained Melody",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Careless Whisper",
      "Let's Get It On",
      "The Lady In Red"
    ],
    "question": "Which Song Ends With The Line \"God Speed Your Love To Me\"? ",
    "tags": ["songs", "lyrics", "music"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9505a3",
    "correctAnswer": "Grasses",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Existence", "Clouds", "The Brain"],
    "question": "What is Agrostology the study of?",
    "tags": ["words", "science"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff95",
    "correctAnswer": "The Byrds",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Hollies",
      "The Cranberries",
      "Buffalo Springfield"
    ],
    "question": "David Crosby, of Crosby, Stills and Nash, was previously with which other popular 60's group?",
    "tags": ["bands", "musicians", "music"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffa1",
    "correctAnswer": "Brussels",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Antwerp", "Ghent", "Liège"],
    "question": "What is the capital of Belgium?",
    "tags": ["capital_cities", "europe", "geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95109e",
    "correctAnswer": "20 months",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["12 months", "24 months", "16 months"],
    "question": "What is the gestation period of an Asian Elephant? ",
    "tags": ["science"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951799",
    "correctAnswer": "Vertigo",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Insomnia", "Nausea", "Headache"],
    "question": "Which of these is a movie directed by Alfred Hitchcock?",
    "tags": ["film"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa51",
    "correctAnswer": "Impressionism",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Abstract expressionism",
      "Italian Renaissance",
      "Modernism"
    ],
    "question": "The painting \"Water Lilies\" by Claude Monet is a part of which art movement?",
    "tags": ["art", "painting", "arts_and_literature"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950282",
    "correctAnswer": "Greece ",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["India", "Morocco", "Russia"],
    "question": "Where Might You Be Offered Ouzo?",
    "tags": ["drink", "general_knowledge", "food_and_drink"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb13",
    "correctAnswer": "Halle Berry",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Judi Dench", "Nicole Kidman", "Sissy Spacek"],
    "question": "Who won the 2001 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Leticia Musgrove in Monster's Ball?",
    "tags": ["acting", "academy_awards", "film", "film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  }
]
